And and and are with us
For the entire nation from Marya Dharma
Babar bhai, now Rizwan bhai has grown to know you
But Babar Bhai
What can you say?
A question is often asked
That when the sound is coming from all sides
Babar Babar
How does Babar fail?
First of all, Aslam Alaikum to all
Thank you for speaking up
People love
And that's what we play for
And proud moments happen
Thank you thank you so much
This love is undiminished
I know that
Thank you GG Kandio
We play for love
And this support is needed
To the entire team, to the Pakistan team
And as far as this tedum is concerned
And create a new Tedam
And let's enjoy it too
We have a little difference
Pleinian came to this site
And try to give your base
In this match and in the Champet Trophy
All you need
Need that
There is a throat
From the people of Karachi that they are in Karachi
They don't come to watch the match
Thus all these people have come
For the opening ceremony
So we are expecting you too
Come and enjoy as many matches as there are
And let's enjoy it too
Surely, after you say this, the whole field
It's going to fill up because people love confidence
They do so much