You know, I don't think people would believe it, but I think it's self-taught.
I don't think confidence is something that you are born with.
I don't think confidence is, it's a skill set.
And I had no confidence growing up.
As a child, I had very low self-esteem.
I was gawky as a teenager.
I lived in America.
I was made to feel conscious about the fact that I was Indian.
That was weird at that time.
And not by everyone, but just by like a few bullies at school that hated me.
High school is hard for everyone.
But so I was in a very weird sort of teenage place.
And when Miss India happened, I mean, inherently competitive.
I think the fact that I was competitive pushed me to teach myself to be confident.
Initially, I faked it until I made it.
I was just like, I'm not going to let anyone see that I'm scared.
I'm not going to let anyone see that I'm affected.
And over time, I realized like as a woman, as a girl in this world,
if I allow myself to be hurt or if I allow myself to be affected,
that's all I'm going to be.
And I'm not trying to say that it's an issue that just women have.
It's not easy to be a woman and show business.
And especially a woman who's opinionated, especially someone who,
I'm not, I'm sort of like, and I wasn't like that from the beginning.
I sort of learned.
So confidence is something I taught myself over the years.
I started becoming okay with who I am.
I became the best version of me.
And then I sort of said, I'm okay.
You know, I'm all right.
Even if someone else thinks this, I'm okay.
And everyone can do that.
People just don't realize that.
I was always creative in school, but I didn't know what to do with it.
I used to write, I did plays, I would do school,
but my aspiration was never to be creative.
And now that I found this vocation, I'm producing, I write columns,
my creativity comes out in whatever way it can.
And I think somehow something guides you.
What that is, I don't know.
I don't have a name for it.
I don't think it's a religion.
I don't know if it's God.
I don't know what it is.
I think something is bigger than us.
And I believe in that.
Well, when I became Miss India, I sort of was on strange ground myself
because I was literally, I was in college, I was studying.
And now I'm suddenly Miss World.
And I have these, I was traveling all over the world, you know,
being an ambassador.
And suddenly, movie offers started coming to me from India.
Because I think producers thought that it would make business sense to,
you know, have Miss World in the movie.
And I guess it did.
Because in my first, second films, like I won a lot of awards,
I didn't think I could act.
I just went in there with the idea of, okay, I can learn a new skill set.
I may not know what acting is about, but I can learn.
So that's how I taught myself.
I've never been to film school.
I taught my career has been in my film school.
I've fallen down and dusted myself off.
I've been okay to fail.
I don't like failure.
I'll never let the same failure happen to me again.
Because I learn from it.
I like knowledge.
I like learning from the people around me.
And I don't think anyone reaches a point no matter how successful you are in life,
or you can't learn something again.
And I think that sort of got me to where I am.
And that's been a big part of my work as a thing.
I remember when no one wanted to ask me a thing.
And I get that.
I remember when, and I still am.
Like sometimes there's so many fights that I do.
But I remember when nobody wanted to do, you know, want in my opinion.
Or I remember when I had to work on, when I was just the side chick to the guy.
And I had to work and do small but important significant parts to prove that I can.
And I will.
And then try.
So no one can be that.
You can't be like, oh, Destiny's going to knock on my door one day.
No, it won't.
You have to be able to recognize opportunities.
Because there'll be a lot of them that come into your life.
And once you recognize an opportunity, you have to seize the day.
And work and bloody hard.
Because there'll be 25 other people you want to do.
I was told that I wanted because of confidence.
Because I asked later, there was so many more beautiful women than me.
But of course, I was curious.
So I was like, well, what is it?
And they were like, just, even you speak, you're just eloquent and confident.
And I was 18 and I realized how important it was.
And I was in this world at 18, just because I was confident.
So it made me understand that confidence truly is the key to getting ahead in life.
If you believe in yourself, the world will believe in you.
Because perception is reality.
And I realized that confidence is reality.