I don't think people would believe it, but I think it's self-taught.
I don't think confidence growing up as a child, I had very low self-esteem, that was weird
at that time and not be confident.
Initially I faked it till I made it.
I would just allow myself to be hurt or if I allow myself to be affected, that's all
you know trying to say that it's an issue that just women have.
It's not easy to be a woman, I wasn't like that from the beginning, I sort of learned.
So confidence is something I taught myself over the end.
I became the best version of me and then I sort of said school, but my aspiration was never
to be creative.
And now that I found this bookating, I write columns, my creativity comes out in whatever way.
It became a sin, I sort of was on strange ground myself because I'm being an ambassador
and suddenly movie offers start to come and make business sense to you know have this world
in the movie and I taught my career has been my first.
I've fallen down, I've dusted myself and I have to work and do small but important
significant parts to prove that there's nothing in an awkward my day or one day, no at all.
You have to be able to recognise opportunities, recognise an opportunity, you have to see the day
and work in bloody hard because there'll be 25 of them.
That I wanted because of confidence because I asked later there was so many more beautiful women
that you're just eloquent and confident and you know and I was 18 and I realised how